Guide to the Percy Simpson Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence
  - Everett, E.M.
    Asks Simpson to suggest a time and date to copy the MS in
    question.
  - Fearnsides, Beatrix
    - ALS to Percy Simpson 1947 Aug 10, Sutton 4 p. 18 x 14 cm Thanks Simpson for good wishes 1951 Mar 11, Sheffield 4 p. 18 x 14 cm Thanks him for accepting Charnwood book (Box 9)
  - Fellowes, Edmund Horace, 1860- Osborn pe 382
    1926 May 22, Windsor Castle
    4 p. 15 x 10 cm
    Query on English madrigals
    1926 May 25, Windsor Castle
    1926 July 29, Windsor Castle
    3 p. 15 x 10 cm
    1927 May 14, Windsor Castle
    1 p. 12 x 9 cm
    Note on madrigals
    1940 May 6, Windsor Castle
    Query on growth of 16th c. literature
    1947 July 17, Windsor Castle Osborn pe 382
    1 p. 14 x 18 cm
    Query on madrigals
  - Fincham, Francis
    1920 Sep 20, London
    1 p. 12 x 20 cm
    Note on parish registers
    1920 Oct 15, London
    Thanks Simpson for help with paper
    1921 Apr 27, London
    Note on Ben Jonson reference in parish registers
    1921 Dec 29, London
    Note on his paper, delivered before the R.H.S. 14 Apr,
    1921
  - Firth, Sir Charles Harding, 1857-1936
    1924 Dec 13, Oxford
    Discusses G.C. Moore Smith's proposed work on Randolf
    1925 Apr 14, Oxford
    Encloses book on life of Mary Wollstonecraft [wanting]
    1925 Jul 11, Oxford
    Thanks Simpson for 2 vols of Ben Jonson
    1929 Dec 26, Oxford
    Wishes Simpson better health
  - Ford, Herbert L.
    1941 Apr 9, Mevagissey
    2 p. 21 x 13
    Information on Jonson 1616 watermarks
  - Forster, Max
    1930 Apr 2, Munich
    Thanks Simpson for 2 papers
  - Foster, Sir William, 1863- Osborn pe 396/1
    1941 Jun 19, London
    Query on name "Hans Beerpot"
  - Francis, Sir Frank Charlton, 1901-
    1952 Mar 8, London
    1 p. 21 x 17 cm
    Thanks Simpson for copy of De la Chapele's Amours de Catulle
  - Froude, Henry
    1910 Jan 11, London
    Encloses 2 copies of missing plate to Campion
  - Furnivall, Frederick James, 1825-1910
    1910 Jan 29, London
  - Garrod, Heathcote William, 1878-1960
    1924 Oct 10, Oxford
    Invites Simpson to dine
    1924 Oct 30, Oxford
    Declines Simpson's invitation
    Letter to [George] Gordon
    1928 Feb 23, Oxford
    Questions one point in Simpson's translation
    1928 May 3, Oxford
    Note on Recordare 1930 Jun 17, Oxford
    Congratulates Simpson on Goldsmith Rendership
    1940 Mar 1, Oxford [not signed]
    2 p. 21 x 11 cm
    Offers his opinion on initials
    1945 Nov 1, Oxford
    Offers his best wishes
  - Gibson, Strickland, 1877- Osborn pe 399
    1955 Apr 12, Oxford
    Sends copy of Plimpton's Education of Shakespeare
  - Gosling, Bernard
    1948 Nov 17, Oxford
    1 p. 17 x 21 cm
    Wishes to discuss facsimiles for Vol. 9
  - Graves, Robert, 1895-
    M/D, N/P
    2 p. 21 x 16 cm
    Gives Simpson information on his recent work
  - Greastead, L.W.
    1949 Nov 18, Oxford
    Information on Latin source of "canker-worm" topos
  - Greg, Sir Walter Wilson, 1875-1959
    1914 May 20, Wimbledon
    Discusses bibliographical innovations
    [1914] May 22, Wimbledon
    Grants Simpson permission to show letter to Chapman
    1917 Jan 22, Wimbledon Osborn pe 396
    Note on article in Library v. 2 (July 1911)
    1919 Nov 15, Wimbledon
    Criticisms of Everyman edition
    1921 Apr 10, Wimbledon
    Note on Everyman 1922 May 3, Wimbledon
    Supports publication of transcription
    1925 Apr 6, Wimbledon
    Thanks Simpson for criticisms of Jonson theories
    1925 May 1, Wimbledon
    Accepts invitation to stay at Oriel
    1925 Jul 6, Meiringen, Germany
    Thanks Simpson for Jonson volumes
    1925 Aug 5, Wimbledon
    1925 Aug 22, Wimbledon
    6 p. 18 x 12 cm
    Queries in Jonson vols I - II
    1925 Oct 3, Wimbledon
    Suggests he check proofs if using Malone E.M.O.
    1926 Mar 2, Wimbledon
    Promises to help on Jasper Mayne [1604-72] project
    1926 Dec 9, Wimbledon
    Discusses possible variants of The Case is Altered 1927 Apr 25, Wimbledon
    Discusses quarto-folio variants
    1929 Jan 12, Wimbledon
    Offers a photo of new Jonson portrait
    1934 Jul 25, Wimbledon
    Asks Simpson's opinion on Digby matter
    ALS to Evelyn Simpson
    1934 Sep 18, Wimbledon
    Offers notes on Jonson bibliography
    1934 Oct 28, Wimbledon
    Notes on bibliographical point
    1937 Mar 30, Wimbledon
    Discusses his critique of Jonson vols.
    1945 Oct 29, Petworth
    2 p. 11 x 18 cm
    Wishes Simpson a happy 80th birthday
    1951 Aug 28, Petworth
    Comments on his review of Jonson
    1951 Oct 21, Petworth
    5 p. 23 x 18 cm
    Discusses Jonson publication history
    1957 Sep 14, Petworth
    5 p. 14 x 21 cm
    Comment on Crooke-Sergier Masques
    1957 Oct 3, Petworth
    2 p. 14 x 21 cm
    Suggests reading of last line of IX.103
    Comments on Jonson; case of Thomas Wise
    1930 Oct 16, London
    Discusses 1616 and 1640 Epigrams 1930 Oct 22, London
    Discusses Thorpe catalogue
    1938 Nov 2, London
    6 p. 25 x 19 cm
    Comments on Simpson's introduction
    1951 Feb 17, Petworth
    1 p. 9 x 15 cm
    Note on Jonson v.IX, 17
    1951 Feb 2, Petworth
    Note on Jonson v. IX, 129
    1951 Jun 14, Petworth
  - Grierson, Herbert John Clifford, 1866-1960
    1911 May 19, Aberdeen
    5 p. 18 x 12 cm
  - Gunston, R.J.
    1894 Dec 28, Hatfield
    Grants him permission to see Jonson MSS
    1895 Mar 29, London
    Will allow access to Jonson MSS
    1895 Apr 16, Hatfield
    Suggests date to see Jonson MSS
    1920 Sep 14, Hatfield
    Encloses copy of letter [wanting]
  - Hake, Henry Mendelsohn, 1892-
    1924 Feb 16, London
    Asks for estimated length of article
    1924 Mar 13, London
    Notes on publication
    1927 Mar 7, London
    7 p. 18 x 12 cm
    Discusses engraving and frontispiece techniques
    1927 Jul 26, London
    2 p 18 x 12 cm
    Remarks on engraving and engravers
    1934 Dec 7, London
    Discusses portrait of Jonson
    1935 Apr 8, London
    Invites Simpson to see portrait of Jonson
    1940 Feb 13, London
    Discusses engraving techniques
    1944 Jun 25, London
    4 p. 20 x 11 cm
    Discusses portraits
  - Hanna, T.
    1948 Sep 11, Dublin
    Sends photo of Trinity College MS G.2.21
  - Hanson, Laurence William
    1937 Oct 17, London
    Queries Simpson on Jonson's Staple of News
  - Harbottle, H.M.
    1926 Jan 18, Benton
    Discusses publishing laws
    ALS to C.H. Herford
    N/D, Benton
    Notes MSS text
  - Harmsworth, A. Leicester
    1933 Jun 8, Bexhill-on-Sea
    Queries on poems of Southwell
    1933 Jun 10, Bexhill-on-Sea
    Notes on poems of Southwell
  - Harrison, George Bagshawe, 1894- Osborn pe 387
    1934 Apr 3, North Bishop's Stortford
    Discusses Simpson's letter in TLS
  - Hart, E.S.W.
    1920 Sep 13, Guildhall, Westminster
    Offers to copy indictment against Jonson
  - Haselden, Reginald Berti, 1881-
    1938 Mar 5, San Marino
    Permission to reproduce Jonson MS (HM 741)
    1938 Apr 5, San Marino
    Notes on Jonson's hand
  - Herbert, Reginald, Lord, 1880-1960
    1947 Feb 22, Iver
    Thanks Simpson for return of photostats
    1947 Apr 19, Iver
    Thanks Simpson and press for 5 vols of Jonson
  - Herford, Charles Harold, 1853-
    1903 Jun 23, Didsbury, Nanchester
    Asks Simpson to send sample of work; asks to work
    with him on Jonson edition
    1903 Jul 10, Didsbury
    Agrees to co-editorship of Jonson
    1903 Jul 31, Didsbury
    Hopes to meet Simpson in London
    1903 Aug 3, Didsbury
    Agrees to meet Simpson at his home
    1903 Nov 4, Didsbury
    Reports new edition of The Alchemist 1904 Jan 10, Didsbury
    Discusses points in Jonson edition
    1904 Feb 12, Didsbury
    1904 Feb 24, Didsbury
    1904 Apr 1, Cannes
    1 p. 14 x 10 cm
    1904 Apr 20, Didsbury
    Notes on Jonson vols.
    1904 May 9, Didsbury
    1904 May 15, Didsbury
    Accepts invitation for 18 June, 1904
    1905 Jan 11, Didsbury
    1905 Mar 13, Didsbury
    1906 Feb 18, Didsbury
    1906 Dec 26, Didsbury
    1909 Jan 11, Didsbury
    1909 Sep 8, Didsbury
    1910 Feb 21, Didsbury
    1910 Nar 11, Didsbury
    1910 May 25, Didsbury
    1911 Apr 4, Didsbury
    Remarks on Simpson's eyesight, notes on Jonson vols.
    1913 S ep 1, Didsbury
    1913 Oct 4, Didsbury
    1913 Dec 30, Didsbury
    1914 Apr 25, Didsbury
    1914 Oct 1, Didsbury
    Reports feelings on war; notes on Jonson vols and other
    projects
    1915 Jul 14, Didsbury
    1923 Aug 11, Didsbury
    Thanks Simpson for meeting
    1924 Feb 20, Didsbury
    4 p. 17 x 13 cm
    1924 Nar 3, Didsbury
    1924 Dec 2, Didsbury
    4 p. 17 x 14 cm
    Notes on Jonson
    1925 Jul 1, Didsbury
    1926 Aug 31, Didsbury
    1930 Jun 22, Oxford
    Congratulates Simpson on Goldsmith appointment
  - Hole, E.C.
    1955 Aug 8, Malaga
    Sends birthday wishes
  - Holland, D.
    1951 Mar 31, Balcombe
    2 p. 18 x 14 cm
    Notes for Jonson, Vol. IX
  - Holme, Strachan
    1909 Jun 30, Manchester
    Acknowledges that Jonson MS is at Bridgewater offices
    1909 Jul 2, Manchester
    Comments on Jonson MS
  - Horton, Percy
    1952 Nov 19, Oxford
    1 p. 17 x 20 cm
    Comments on portrait to be arranged
    1953 Mar 16, Oxford
    2 p. 17 x 20 cm
    Asks that drawing be allowed to be exhibited at R.A.
    1953 Dec 30, London
    Sends photo of Simpson portrait [enclosed]
  - Hotson, Leslie, 1897-
    1955 Dec 13, Northford, Connecticut
    1 p. 31 x 19 cm
    Comments on notes to Jonson vols
  - Housman, Alfred Edward, 1859-1936
    1923 Feb 24, Cambridge
    Comments on restoration of Jonson's verse
    1923 Mar 2, Cambridge
    Comment on readings circularem and philtram
  - Hughes, Richard Arthur Warren, 1900-1976
    ? Jul 20, Penrhydendracth
    Apologizes for his failure
    ? Sep 10, Penthydendracth
    1 p. 14 x 21 cm
    Thanks Simpson for remarks on his policy
  - Hutchinson, Francis Ernest, 1871-
    1944 Feb 2, Oxford
    2 p. 21 x 18 cm
    Comment on Vaughan letters
    1945 Nov 23, Oxford
    1 p 21 x 18 cm
    Comment on Vaughan text
    1947 May 21, Oxford
  - Jackson, William Alexander, 1905-1964
    1936 May 7, New York
    4 p. 20 x 13 cm
    Misc. notes on Jonson, etc.
    1936 Jun 8, New York
    3 p. 22 x 14 cm
    1953 Mar 24, Cambridge, Mass.
    1 p. 31 x 18 cm
    Misc. notes on new Jonson text
    1936 Jul 7, New York
    3 p. 21 x 13 cm
    Discusses Jonson autographs
    1936 Aug 22, New York
    Sends Pforzheimer Catalog [wanting]
    1936 Sep 27, New York
    Misc. notes on Jonson texts
    1936 Sep 30, New York
    Misc. notes on Jonson texts; with notes by Simpson
    1936 Oct 27, New York
    2 p. 21 x 15 cm
    Thanks Simpson for mention in Jonson 1936 Nov 22, New York
    Note on Jonson library
    1937 Nov 22, New York
    1937 Dec 23, New York
    Notes on Pforzheimer catalog
    1938 Apr 24, London
    Will arrive in Oxford
    1939 Nov 30, Cambridge, Mass.
    Notes on Jonson library
    1942 Jan 20, Cambridge, Mass.
    1943 Jun 28, Cambridge, Mass.
    1944 Jul 7, Cambridge, Mass.
    1944 Oct 3, Cambridge, Mass.
    1944 Oct 14, Cambridge, Mass.
    Note on Jonson signature
    1947 Apr 1, Cambridge, Mass.
    1947 May 21, Cambridge, Mass.
    Notes on Jonson signature
    1948 Jul 19, Cambridge, Mass.
    Note on Otto Vaeneris
    1950 Sep 1, Dublin
  - James, C.W.
    1927 Aug 26, Hockham Wells
    1 p. 19 x 14 cm
    Arranges use of Thomas Porter's Epigrams
    1927 Aug 29, Hockham Wells
    Has dispatched Porter volume to Bodleian
  - Jazle, C.
    1922 Sep 20, Blakeney
    Invites Simpson to use his notes on Jonson
  - Jenkins, Claude, 1877-
    1923 Aug 20, London
    1 p. 20 x 15 cm
    Is sorry not to be of any help on document
  - Jenkinson, Francis John Henry, 1853-1923
    1904 Mar 3, Cambridge
    1 p, 9 x 12 cm
    Reports on Cambridge Library Jonsonian materials
  - Jenkinson, Sir Hilary
    1925 Feb 3, London
    Discusses punctuation; accepts invitation to address
    Biblio. Soc.
    1925 Jul 5, London
    Thanks Simpson for Jonson vols.
    [1944 Nov 27], London
    4 p. 14 x 21 cm
    Textual notes from Public Record Office
    1924 May 15, London, Chelsea
    3 p. 32 x 21 cm
  - Jerrold, Douglas, 1893- Osborn pe 406
    1930 Sep 10, London
    Comment on edition of Masque of Queens
  - Johnson, John de Monins, 1882-1956
    1932 Jun 27, Oxford
    Thanks Simpson for help at O.U.P.
    1937 Dec 7, Oxford
    Asks for Simpson to join appeal for retaining Arts End of
    Bodleian [encl.]
  - Jones, Philip Edmund, 1904-
    Explains reference to "Great Gobletto" in Gyles
    Oldisworth's elegy to Ben Jonson (1627) [cf. TLS 1953, Nov 27]
  - Jones, ?
    1939 Jul 1, Kelston Park
    Discusses Inigo Jones and lineage
    1939 Aug 3, Kelston Park
    Thanks Simpson for safe return of family objects and for
    gift
  - Joseph, Barbara
    1948 May 10, Oxford
    Notes on Cornelii Frontonis de Prenctis (1516)
  - Kenyon, Sir Frederick George, 1863-
    1934 May 28, London
    Invites Simpson to address British Academy
    1934 Jun 1, London
    Is pleased Simpson can accept; leaves topic to him
    1934 Oct 19, London
    Arranges date of lecture
    1935 Apr 4, London
    Asks for summary of lecture
  - Ker, William Paton, 1855-1923
    1919 Sep 25, Corrie
    1 p. 10 x 15 cm
    Discloses title, The Humanist Ideal 1921 May 8, Oxford
    Announces upcoming lecture, "Romantic Fallacies"
  - Keynes, Sir Geoffrey, 1887-
    1926 Apr 15, London
    Comments on proofs
    1926 Apr 23, London
    Comments on proposed edition of letters; looks forward
    to E. Simpson's book
  - Lacey, Norman Osborn pe 386
    1948 Mar 28, London
    Presents copy of his Wordsworth~s View of Nature
  - Larsen, T.
    1929 Oct. 15, London
    Biographical notes on George Peele [with enclosure]
  - Lascelles, Mary
    1947 Jul 28, Oxford
    3 p. 23 x 18 cm
    Offers theory on Jonson's allusions to George Whetstone's Mirror for Magistrates (1555)
  - Latham, Agnes Mary Christabel
    1912 Jun 29, Hampstead
    Presents copy of her book on Raleigh
  - Lee, Sir Sidney, 1859-1926
    1906 Jan 21, Kensington
    Thanks Simpson for Scenes from Old Playbooks
  - Leicester, Sir Thomas William Coke, Earl of, 1848-
    [1927] Jun 25, Holkum Wells
    Asks Simpson to contact C.W. James in London
    [1928] Jan 1, Holkum Wells
    Cannot allow him access to MS until James is well
  - Leischman, James Blair, 1902-1963
    1940 Dec 30, Oxford
    8 p. 18 x 12 cm
    Misc. textual queries
    1941 Oct 20, Southampton
    Notes on Halliwell-Phillips MS
  - Long, Percy Waldron, 1876- Osborn pe 394
    1939 Jan 5, New York
    Informs Simpson of his honorary election to MLA
    1941 Feb 14, New York
  - Low, G.
    1910 Feb 27, London
    Discusses education in Jonson's time
  - Lyell, James Patrick Ronaldson, 1871-1949 Osborn pe 384
  - Lynd, Robert, 1879-1949
    1928 May 1, London
    Asks Simpson for article on Shakespeare textual criticism
    for Encyclopedia Britannica 1928 May 25, London
    Thanks Simpson for interest
    1928 Jul 30, London
    Thanks Simpson for article
  - Lyon, P.C.
    1922 May 27, Oxford
    Notifies Simpson of new Fellows emoluments
  - MacDonald, Allan John, 1887-
    1905 May 11, London
  - MacDonald, Hugh, 1885-
    1926 Oct 27, London
    Notes on ampersand in The Phoenix Nest 1945 Oct 31, Fairholme
    2 p. 20 x 13 cm
    Wishes him happy 80th birthday
    N/D, Cambridge Osborn pe 389
    Presents copy of his Observations Upon A Late Libel
  - McKerrow, Ronald Brunlees, 1872-1940 Osborn pe 392
    1914 Jul 6, Brook Green
    Presents copy of "Notes on Bibliographical Evidence"
    1927 Jun 23, London
    Advises him on S.T.C. transaction
    1934 Oct 23, Wendover
    Comments on Crawford
  - Madan, Falconer, 1851-1935
    1916 Apr 1, Oxford
    Note on F.J. Furnivall
    1921 Apr 22, Oxford
    Congratulates Simpson on Oriel Fellowship
    1922 Nov 22, Oxford
    Discusses standard bibliographic forms [enclosure]
    1926 May 23, Oxford
    Comments on Greg; cannot recover notes on Milton
  - Mallett, Carlie
    Permission to publish The Gipsies Changed (ca 1621)
  - Margoliouth, Herschel Maurice, 1887- Osborn pe 379
    1927 Aug 8, Oxford
    Promises to have a copy of his Andrew Marvell sent
  - Martin, Gibson
    1895 Jun 20, Chatsworth
    Invites Simpson to use Duke of Devonshire's library
  - Martin, Leonard Cyril, 1886-
    1945 Oct 31, West Kirby
  - Masefield, John, 1878-1967
    1920 Apr 27, Oxford
    Accepts Presidency of branch of English Association
    1920 Apr 29, Oxford
    Wishes to know place of next meeting
    1920 May 19, Oxford
    Thanks him for notification of changed date
    1921 Jan 19, Oxford
    Suggests speakers for Association meeting
    ? Nov 22, Oxford
    Asks for topic of de la Mare's speech
    ? Nov 25, Oxford
    Thanks Simpson for tickets
    Invites Simpson to tea
    Thanks Simpson for letter concerning play production
    Thanks Simpson for letter concerning plays
    Discusses upcoming lecture by Rofs
    N/D, Edinburgh
    Asks for addresses of English Association chapters
    in U.K.
  - Maxwell, J.C.
    1946 Nov 23, Oxford
    Discusses stressed and unstressed rhymes in Spenser
    1947 Jan 4, Oxford
    2 p, 21 x 13 cm
  - Mayhew, Anthony Lawson, 1842-
    1914 Jan 18, Oxford
    On definition of estridge in Glossary of Tudor- Stuart Terms
  - Miles, Sir Bernard, 1907
    1953 Jun 11, London
    2 p. 26 x 21
    Thanks Simpson for recognition of Mermaid Theatre
  - Milford, Sir Humphrey Sumner, 1877-
    1903 Nov 25, Oxford
    Discusses upcoming Jonson volume
    1904 Feb 20, Oxford
    Invites Simpson to come to Oxford
    1904 Feb 23, Oxford
    Discusses Jonson volumes
    1904 Feb 25, Oxford
    Note on Jonson volumes
    1904 April 19, Oxford
    1904, May 16, Oxford
    Congratulates Simpson on success
    1904 Dec 20, Oxford
    Promises to send copy of NED
    1905 Jan 11, Oxford
    1905 Feb 13, Oxford
    Publishing note
    1905 May 8, Oxford
    1905 Sep 18, Oxford
    Inquires about forthcoming books on Shakespeare
    and Inigo Jones
  - Morshead, Owen Frederick, 1893-
    1936 Sep 30, Berkshire
    Reports missing Jonson volume
    1937 Jun 24, Windsor Castle, Berkshire
    2 p. 25 x 19 cm
    Notes on Jonson miniatures, volume
    1941 Oct 16, Berkshire
    2 p. 25 x 20 cm
    Describes Reynolds' portrait of Garrick
  - Morison, Stanley, 1889-1967
    1929 Feb 21, London
    Is glad that Simpson likes Ben Jonson's Grammar
  - Mullinger, James Bass, 1834-
    1904 Mar 1, Cambridge
    Will show Simpson St. John's, Camb. Jonson vols.
  - Murray, David Leslie, 1888-
    1938 Jul 14, London
    Is anxious to publish article on Lucy, Countess of
    of Bedford in TLS
  - Needham, Francis
    1928 Dec 20, Worksop
    2 p. 19 x 14 cm
    Discusses portrait [unnamed]
    1939 Oct 23, Workshop
    3 p. 19 x 14 cm
    Enclosed proof [wanting]
  - Newgate, Bernard, H.
    1939 Dec 6, Oxford
    1 p. 21 x 18 cm
    Note on books owned by Lucy, Countess of Bedford
  - Nicholson, Edward Williams Byron, 1849-1912
    1903 Nov 4, Oxford
    Gives Simpson hours of Bodleian
  - Nicholson, F. C.
    1930 Mar 18, Edinburgh
    Note on poem "In praise of Cynthia's Revells"
    1930 Mar 21, Edinburgh
    Note on "In praise of Cynthia's Revells"
  - Northiare, Robert Chalmers, 1st Baron of, 1858-1938
    1926 May 20, Cambridge
    Invites Simpson as overnight guest
    1927 Oct 29, Cambridge
    Invites him for weekend
    1931 Jan 7, Cambridge
    Invites him to inspect a pencil drawing
  - O'Farrell, Nellie McK
    1948 Nov. 27
    [with enclosure]
  - Osborn, James Marshall, 1906-1976
    1955 Apr 18, New Haven
    Thanks Simpson for copy of Studies in Elizabethan Drama
  - Oxley, L. Rice
    1952 Oct 26, Oxford
    Asks Simpson to consent to sitting for portrait
  - Parrod, T.M.
    1942 Jun 29, Princeton
    2 p. 17 x 14 cm
  - Penniman, Josiah Harmar, 1868-
    LS to Percy Simpson [frag.]
    N/D, N/P
    1 p. 14 x 20 cm
    Page 2 of 2 page letter
  - Pforzheimer, Carl H. [Library]
    1940 May 21, Purchase
    Discusses reprint of Time Vindicated 1940 Jul 3, Purchase
    Discusses reprint of Time Vindicated 1941 Jan 6, Purchase
    Will send variants under separate cover
    1942 Feb 27, New York
    Thanks Simpson for letters and for Jonson Vol. 7
    1951 Jan 2, New York
    Thanks Simpson for Jonson Vols. IX and X
  - Phelps, Lancelot Ridley, 1853-
    1924 Sep 3, Oxford
    Thanks Simpson for gift
    1930 Feb 21, Oxford
    Note on George Garrard
    1930 Jun 25, Oxford
    Congratulates Simpson on Goldsmith readership appointment
  - Pinto, V. ae S
    1926 Mar 1, Nottingham
    Sends copy of "Aucassin and Nicolette" [enclosed]
    1943 Dec 31, Nottingham
    Notes on rhymes in Welsh, English, Irish
  - Plummer, R. Charles
    Warns him of closing of Bodleian
  - Poel, William
    1921 Dec 20, London
    Thanks Simpson for Faustus text notes
    1924 Jul 5, London
    Note on the Oxford Playhouse
    1924 Jul 20, London
    With enclosures
    1924 Jul 21, London
    n/d, London
    Asks for suggestions on performance of Fratricide Punished
  - Pollard, Alfred William, 1859-1944
    1915 Oct 16, London
    Comments on Simpson's Everyman in his Humour 1923 Nov 23, London
    Misc. notes
    ? May 31, London
    Notifies him of library of the English School elections
  - Poole, Reginald Lane, 1857-
    1922 Jan 27, Oxford
    Grants permission to publish
    Has Donne documents
    1922 Dec 13, Oxford
  - Powell, F. John
    1904 Apr 12, Oxford
    1 p. 15 x 25 cm
    Cannot host Simpson
  - Powicke, J.W.
    On behalf of Oriel College fellows, wishes happy birthday
  - Raleigh, Sir Walter Alexander, 1861-
    - ALS to Percy Simpson 1910 Mar 15, Ferry Hinksey 2 p. 21 x 13 cm Discusses English Association, other topics 1913 Jul 26, Ferry Hinksey 4 p. 21 x 13 cm Discusses possibilities of lectureship and teaching position (Box 10)
    - 1913 Sep 4, Ferry Hinksey 2 p. 21 x 13 cm Has tried to arrange pupils for Simpson 1913 Oct 26, Ferry Hinksey 2 p. 23 x 18 cm Invites Simpson to dine 1914 Mar 27, Ferry Hinksey 2 p. 21 x 13 cm Discusses press work
    - 1914 Jun 7, Ferry Hinksey 3 p. 21 x 13 cm Explains the pending vote on "lecturer" position 1915 Jan 15, Ferry Hinksey 2 p. 21 x 13 cm Discusses Wordsworth's punctuation [ TLS proof enclosed] 1916 Apr 19, Ferry Hinksey 2 p. 21 x 13 cm Invites Simpson to lunch or dinner 1916 Jun 14, Ferry Hinksey 4 p. 21 x 13 cm Questions Simpson on use of press rooms
    - 1916 Nov 18, Ferry Hinksey 2 p. 21 x 13 cm Discusses Oxford rules [ALS from Wyld to Raleigh, 17 Nov 1916 enclosed] 1918 Feb 21, Ferry Hinksey 2 p. 21 x 13 cm Plans to meet George Thorn-Drury in London
  - Reyher, Paul, 1876-
    1909 Jul 2, Bordeaux
    Presents copy of his Les Masques Anglais 1924 Dec 3, Nancy
    Thanks Simpson for offer of books; renews acquaintance
    1925 Jan 4, Nancy
    Thanks Simpson for gift of books
  - Reynolds, George Fullmer, 1877-
    1932 Dec 13, Boulder, Colorado
    Note on Heywood's The Royal King and Loyal Subject (1637)
  - Richmond, Bruce Lyttleton, 1871-
    1930 Feb 12, London
    Wishes to see article for TLS 1932 Feb 16, London
    Will print article, but only as letter to editor
  - Roberts, Sir Sidney Castle, 1887-1966
    1942 Sep 18, Cambridge
    Grants permission to use Sparrow edition of Donne
    1951 Feb 13, Cambridge Simpson Box 1
    Inquires whether Simpson will accept Honorary
    Cambridge degree
  - Robinson, Philip
    1936 May 6, London
    Note on Jonson folio leaf
  - Rouse, William Henry Denham, 1863-
    1939 Aug 7, Cambridge
    Inquires about Simpson's book on Elizabethan
    punctuation
    1939 Aug 11, Cambridge
    Will get copy of Elizabethan Punctuation from library
  - Sackville, Lionel Edward Sackville-West, Baron, 1867-
    1925 Mar 4, Sevenoaks, Kent